{"data":[{"question":"To check out of a hotel is to ________.","a":"register it","b":"leave it","c":"complain","d":"ask for a room","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Check out: to leave a hotel after paying the bill.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Children under the age of eight ________ allowed to participate this game.","a":"hasn't","b":"haven't","c":"isn't","d":"aren't","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Passive voice: Be + PP.\u00a0\n- Children: plural noun- are.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Employers often require that candidates have not only a degree ________.","a":"but two years experience","b":"also two years experience","c":"but also two-year experience","d":"but more two years experience","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Not only ... (but) also ...: in addition to being or doing something.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Today the noise and smoke of factories ________ the environment polluted.","a":"make","b":"makes","c":"want","d":"wants","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Subject (the noise and smoke of factories ) is plural.\u00a0\n- Make sbd\/sth + Noun\/adj: to cause something to happen, or cause a particular state or condition.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Neither oil nor coal ________ used to produce electricity.","a":"was","b":"are","c":"is","d":"were","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Two singular subjects connected by either\/or or neither\/nor require a singular verb.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"None of us ________ agreed with his thought.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"has","d":"have","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: Have\/has + PP.\u00a0\n- Subject (None of us) is plural.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Not only these boys but also that girl ________ to class late.","a":"come","b":"comes","c":"has","d":"have","answer":"2","explain":"\n- If you use either-or, neither- nor, not only- but also look at the subject closest to the verb, the subject closest to the verb determines whether the verb is singular or plural.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Neither of these documents ________ translated into English.","a":"was","b":"need","c":"were","d":"needs","answer":"1","explain":"\n- When\u00a0either and neither are subjects, they always take singular verbs.\n\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"The first transatlantic telephone cable system was not established _______ 1956.","a":"while","b":"until","c":"on","d":"when","answer":"2","explain":"\n- When\/while + clause.\u00a0\n- On+ specific date.\u00a0\n- In, until + year.\u00a0\n- Until: if something happens until a particular time, it continues and then stops at that time.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"},{"question":"Soap operas, a type of television drama series, are so called because at first, they were ________.","a":"often which soap manufacturers sponsored","b":"sponsored often soap manufacturers","c":"often sponsored by soap manufacturers","d":"soap manufacturers often sponsored them","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Passive voice: Be + PP + By + object.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"37","type":"1"}]}